Radio DJ:
All right, I know
that special someone
you've been dreaming about
all night long
is right next to you
right now.
The new one from Selena,
it's called "Dreaming of You."
♪ Late at night when
all the world ♪
♪ Is sleeping ♪
♪ I stay up
and think of you ♪
♪ And I wish on a star ♪
♪ That somewhere you are
thinking of me too ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm dreaming ♪
♪ Of you tonight ♪
♪ 'Til tomorrow ♪
♪ I'll be
holding you tight ♪
♪ And there's nowhere
in the world ♪
♪ I'd rather be ♪
♪ Than here in my room ♪
♪ Dreaming about
you and me ♪
♪ Wonder if you
ever see me ♪
♪ And I wonder
if you know I'm there ♪
♪ Am I there?
Am I? ♪
♪ If you looked
in my eyes ♪
♪ Would you see
what's inside ♪
♪ Would you even care? ♪
♪ I just wanna
hold you close ♪
♪ But so far ♪
♪ All I have
are dreams of you ♪
♪ So I wait for the day ♪
♪ And the courage to say ♪
♪ How much I love you ♪
♪ Yes I do ♪
♪ I'll be dreaming ♪
♪ Of you tonight ♪
- ♪ 'Til tomorrow ♪
♪ I'll be
holding you tight ♪
♪ And there's nowhere
in the world ♪
- ♪ I'd rather be ♪
- ( car honks )
♪ Than here in my room ♪
♪ Dreaming about
you and me ♪
♪ Ah ah ♪
♪ Corazón ♪
♪ I can't stop
dreaming of you ♪
♪ No puedo dejar
de pensar en ti ♪
♪ I can't stop
dreaming ♪
♪ Cómo te necesito ♪
♪ I can't stop
dreaming of you ♪
♪ Mi amor,
cómo te extraño ♪
♪ Late at night
when all the world ♪
♪ Is sleeping ♪
♪ I stay up
and think of you ♪
♪ And I still can't
believe ♪
♪ That you came up to me ♪
♪ And said, "I love you" ♪
♪ I love you too ♪
♪ Now I'm dreaming ♪
♪ With you tonight ♪
- ♪ 'Til tomorrow ♪
♪ And for all of my life ♪
♪ And there's nowhere
in the world ♪
♪ I'd rather be ♪
♪ Than here in my room ♪
♪ Dreaming with you
endlessly ♪
♪ Dreaming
of you tonight ♪
♪ With you tonight ♪
♪ 'Til tomorrow, I'll be
holding you tight ♪
♪ And there's nowhere
in the world ♪
♪ I'd rather be ♪
♪ Tonight. ♪
Radio DJ:
All right, I know
that special someone
that's close to your heart,
that you've been dreaming
about all night
is right next to you,
right now.
And we hope we took care of you
with the new one from Selena,
called "Dreaming of You."